tbits.me 2017-07-13

# Tradable Bits Privacy Policy

Tradable Bits will be collecting information from user sessions to ensure that our applications and platform are built as powerfully as possible and provide the best user experience. The information collected will be used to improve our services including any web page enhancements, quality increases and to ensure strict security controls. Please note that this privacy policy applies only to information submitted and collected online through our website. It does not apply to information that you may submit to us offline, or to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we may link. We do not share or sell any information collected on our sites with the exception of the following we may provide: 

1) Statistics and data collected for the sites a customer administrates and manages where they have rights and commercial access for the Pages, domains and accounts. 

2) Share data and information when necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. 

3) Data and information will be shared within Tradable Bits Ltd and its partners to enhance services and application and platform development. All of this data will be anonymized and will not disclose any personally identifiable information about any particular user. 

What do we collect? 

We will collect names, emails and/or phone numbers for those who register and communicate with us. We will also collect statistics on Tradable Bits Platform usage including but not limited to apps (campaign) page views, social login, comments and track time/clicks. We also may collect IP addresses, browser types, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. When you register we will collect your Full Name, Email, Phone, Business/Corporation Name, Billing Address and Credit Card information for those who use our Enhanced Services. This information is used to keep track of user accounts, billing information, identification, authorization, authentication, products/services activation, service enhancement, research and control rights. 

Children 

Tradable Bits does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. This is not a website directed to children. If you are under 13 years of age you should not use this website, and under no circumstances should you send information about yourself to Tradable Bits. If Tradable Bits discovers that a child has provided Tradable Bits with personally identifiable information, Tradable Bits will immediately delete that child’s personally identifiable information from the website. 

Cookies 

A cookie is a small amount of data that often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies may be required to use the Tradable Bits service. We may use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. 

Company Data & Safeguards 

In accordance with the agreement between Tradable Bits and Company, Company exclusively owns all rights, titles and interest in the content and any personal information made available through the Tradable Bits Platform (“Company Data”). Tradable Bits maintains appropriate organizational and technical safeguards for the protection of the security, confidentiality and integrity of Company Data. Those safeguards will include, but will not be limited to, measures intended to prevent unauthorized access to, use of, modification or disclosure of Company Data. 

Data Storage 

Tradable Bits complies with the Canadian PIPEDA (Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act) to ensure the protection of individual information collected is protected and secure. The European Commission has recognised that the Canadian Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act provides adequate protection for certain personal data transferred from the EU to Canada. This will allow certain personal data to flow freely from the EU to recipients in Canada subject to the Canadian Act, without additional safeguards being needed to meet the requirements of the EU Data Protection Directive. The decision fulfils an undertaking made in 1999 by Canada and the EU in their "Joint Statement on Electronic Commerce in the Global Information Society". Both parties promised to work together to build confidence in cross-border electronic commerce and to ensure the free flow of personal data on the basis of high data protection standards. 

Tradable Bits uses vendor and 3rd party hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Tradable Bits Platform and services. Tradable Bits owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Tradable Bits application, however, you retain all rights to your own data. All data collected is stored and hosted in Canada. 

Disclosure 

Tradable Bits may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service. 

Changes to Privacy Policy 

We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time. If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our website so that you and other users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. You should also check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes. If we are going to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you and others via email or by placing a prominent notice on our website. By using this website, you signify your assent to the Tradable Bits Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not use this website or our applications (campaigns). Your continued use of this website or applications (campaigns) will signify your acceptance of these changes. 

####  Tradable Bits Privacy Policy was updated on May 12, 2015. 

"Tradable Bits" is defined as Tradable Bits Media Inc, the owner and creator of the Tradable Bits platform and all included services: apps (campaigns), Stream, Fan CRM, etc.  
"Company" is any client of Tradable Bits who uses or has a licence to use the Tradable Bits platform on behalf of another entity.  
“Person" is the end user who interacts with the Company through the Tradable Bits platform, thus extending their personally identifiable information to the Company via Tradable Bits.
